kohlscorporation.com 2019-11-17

# KOHL'S PRIVACY POLICY - YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS | Kohl's

Effective Date: November 15, 2019

## SCOPE

This Privacy Policy describes how Kohl's Department Stores, Inc., its affiliates and some of its third-party service providers treat customer personal information on the websites and apps where this Privacy Policy is located. In this Privacy Policy we call websites, emails and apps “Platforms.” And when we say “Kohl's” or “we”, we mean us, our affiliates, and relevant third-party service providers. This Privacy Policy also applies to how we treat personal information collected in Kohl's retail stores and Kohl's operated retail outlet locations. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided directly to our banking partner, which offers the Kohl's Charge credit card. To view the separate Kohl's Charge credit card Privacy Policy that describes how our banking partner uses your information in connection with the Kohl's Charge credit card, please click [here](https://corporate.kohls.com/Legal/CapOnePolicy.pdf).

By using the Platforms and shopping in our Stores, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

Back to Top

## TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Kohl's collects information from you and about you. This may include:

  * **Identifying Information.** For example, we may collect your name, unique personal identifier, online identifier, mailing address, email address, postal address and telephone number, including your mobile phone number.
  * **Payment Information.** For example, we may collect your credit card number and billing address.
  * **Information You Post.** For example, we may collect information you post in a public space on our site. This may include our Ratings & Reviews feature. 
  * **Social Media Information.** We may collect information you post on our social media pages. We may also collect your social media profile information.
  * **Event Information.** For example, we may collect the mailing address associated with your event registry.
  * **Information You Submit.** For example, we may collect information when you contact us through the “Live Chat” feature on our site. We may also collect information submitted in connection with creating an account, completing an application, placing an order or making a purchase, including bank account numbers or other financial information. 
  * **Demographic Information.** For example, we may collect your age, gender and zip code. 
  * **Driver's License Information.** To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may collect your driver’s license information. For example, we may collect this information if you return an item without a receipt. 
  * **Device Information.** For example, we may collect the type of device you use to access our Platforms. It may also include your device identification number, IP address or mobile operating system.
  * **Location Information.** For example, we may collect precise location information from your device. This may include your in-store location. For more information about your choices related to location information, see the Choices section below.
  * **Commercial Information.** For example, we may collect information about the products or services purchased, obtained or considered, as well as other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
  * **Internet or other Network Activity Information.** For example, we may collect information related to your browsing history, search history and other information regarding your interactions with our Platforms or advertisements.
  * **Other Information.** If you use our website, we may collect information about the browser you are using. We may look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our app, we may look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it. If you visit our stores, we may capture audio, electronic, visual, thermal or similar information with our surveillance equipment.

Back to Top

## HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION

Kohl's collects information in different ways. 

**Directly From You.** For example, when you:

  * Make a purchase in our Stores or on our Platform. 
  * Make a return or exchange.
  * Purchase an electronic gift card.
  * Create a personalized Kohls.com shopping account. 
  * Track an order online. 
  * Sign up to receive promotional emails or text messages (including offers and sales alerts). 
  * Sign up to join a loyalty, rewards or similar program or club.
  * Provide your contact information to our beauty associates.
  * Participate in one of our promotional sweepstakes, contests, surveys or focus groups.
  * Create or update a gift registry.
  * Use the Ratings & Reviews or related services and features.
  * Submit a request to our Customer Service team.
  * Sign up for, and/or maintain, a Kohl's Charge card.
  * Interact with Kohl's social media pages.

**Passively.** For example, when you:

  * Install and use Kohl's mobile apps. 
  * Visit and navigate Kohl's Platforms on any device.
  * Enable location-based features on our Platforms.
  * Click on sponsored links or third-party advertisements. 
  * Use the Wi-Fi Services provided in some Stores. 
  * Visit Stores; Kohl's uses cameras in and around its Stores for security and operational purposes.
  * Receive or interact with Kohl's communications and Platforms that may contain cookies or pixels.

**From Third Parties.** We may receive information about you from other sources. For example, this may include receiving information from:

  * Our business partners, including online advertising networks and companies that co-sponsor our promotions. 
  * Social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Pinterest and Instagram.
  * Companies that provide information to supplement what we already know about you, including data brokers. 

**By Combining Information.** For example, we may:

  * Combine information that we collect in our stores with information we collect through our Platforms. 
  * Combine information we collect about you from the different devices you use to access our Platforms.
  * Combine information we get from third parties with information we already have about you. 

Back to Top

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Examples of how we may use your information include:

_Business Purposes:_

  * **To Provide Our Products and Services.** This could include fulfilling your requests for products or services. It could also include processing purchases or return transactions. 
  * **To Improve Our Products and Services.** We may use your information to make our Platforms and stores better. We may also use your information to customize your experience with us.
  * **To Understand Your Interests.** For example, we may use your information to better understand what products interest you based on information we collect about you and your household.
  * **To Respond to Your Requests or Questions.** This may include responding to your customer feedback. 
  * **To Communicate With You.** We may communicate with you about your account or our relationship. We may also contact you about this Privacy Policy or our Platform Terms & Conditions.
  * **For Security Purposes.** This could include protecting our company and our customers. It may also include protecting our Platforms.

_Commercial Purposes:_

  * **For Marketing Purposes.** We may provide you with information about new products and special offers. We may use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. We may tell you about new features or updates. These might be third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. For more information about your choices related to these communications, see the Choices section below. 
  * **To Send Push Notifications.** If you use our mobile apps, we may send you push notifications about new products or special offers.

_Additional Purposes:_

  * **As Otherwise Permitted By Law or As We May Notify You.**

Back to Top

We may share your information in the following ways:

  * **Internally.** We may share your information within the Kohl's family of companies. This includes our affiliates.
  * **On our Platforms.** For example, we may display information you post on our Ratings & Reviews feature. We may also display information you choose to share on your event registry.
  * **With Our Service Providers.** We may share your information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, this may include merchandise vendors and payment processors. It may also include companies that send emails on our behalf.
  * **With Our Business Partners.** For example, this may include third parties that provide financial products and services related to our business, including Kohl's Charge credit card. It may also include a third party that co-sponsors a contest or promotion.
  * **With Third Parties for Marketing Purposes.** This may include third parties in whose products or services we believe you may be interested. These third parties may also share your information with others. These third parties may use your information for their own marketing purposes or the marketing purposes of others. This may include the delivery of interest-based advertising.
  * **With Any Successors to All or Part of Our Business.** For example, if Kohl's merges with, acquires or is acquired by another business entity. This may include an asset sale, corporate reorganization or other change of control.
  * **To Comply With the Law or To Protect Ourselves.** For example, this could include responding to a court order or subpoena. It could also include sharing information if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We may share information when we are investigating a potential fraud. This could include fraud we think has occurred during a sweepstakes or promotion. We may also share information if you are the winner of a sweepstakes or other contest with anyone who requests a winner’s list.
  * **For Other Reasons We May Describe to You.**

Back to Top

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please contact us as described in the How to Contact Us section, below. Indicate in your email or letter that you are a California resident making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. 

**California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018.** Effective January 1, 2020, if you reside in California, then you have the following rights:

You have the right to opt-out of Kohl's sale of your personal information.

You have the right to request the deletion of your personal information.

You have the right to request us to disclose to you the following, no more than twice in a 12-month period:

  1. Categories of personal information we collected about you during the preceding 12 months.
  2. Categories of sources from which we collected the personal information during the preceding 12 months.
  3. Business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling your personal information during the preceding 12 months.
  4. Categories of third parties with whom we share the personal information during the preceding 12 months.
  5. Specific pieces of personal information we collected about you during the preceding 12 months.

You have the right to request us to disclose to you the following, no more than twice in a 12-month period:

  1. Categories of personal information we collected about you during the preceding 12 months.
  2. Categories of personal information we have sold and categories of third parties to whom the information was sold during the preceding 12 months.
  3. Categories of personal information we disclosed about you for a business purpose during the preceding 12 months.

We will not discriminate against you because you exercised your rights under this section of the Privacy Policy.

For purposes of exercising your rights above, please note the following regarding how we collect and use your personal information as described in this policy:

  * **We collect the following categories of personal information:** Identifiers; payment information; characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law; commercial information; professional or employment information; internet of other electronic network activity information; geolocation data; audio, electronic or visual information.
  * **We disclose the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:** Identifiers; payment information; commercial information; professional or employment information; internet of other electronic network activity information; geolocation data; audio, electronic or visual information.
  * **We sell the following categories of personal information:** Identifiers; commercial information; Internet or other electronic network activity; geolocation data.

To learn more about submitting a request under this section of the Privacy Policy, please see the How to Contact Us section, below. 

Back to Top

## CHILDREN UNDER 16

Our Platforms where this Privacy Policy is located are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable data from persons under the age of 16, and strive to comply with the provisions of COPPA (The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 16 has provided us with information, please contact us at [privacy@kohls.com](mailto:privacy@kohls.com). You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this website Policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [ here](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online) to view the FTC's guide to protecting your child's privacy online.

Back to Top

## SECURITY

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. We use reasonable means to safeguard personal information under our control. A user id and a password are needed to access certain areas of the Kohl's Platforms. It is your responsibility to protect your username and password.

Back to Top

## STORAGE OF INFORMATION

Information we maintain may be stored in the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your personal information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not provide the same level of protections as those in your own country

Back to Top

## LINKS

Kohl's Platforms may contain links to other third-party sites that are not governed by this Privacy Policy. If you click on a link to a third-party site, you will be taken to a site we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices used by third-party sites. We suggest that you read the privacy policies of those sites carefully. We are not responsible for these third-party sites.

Back to Top

## HOW TO CONTACT US

If you wish to contact us to update your information, please feel free to contact us by telephone at 866-887-8884.

Effective January 1, 2020, if you wish to contact us to submit a request under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, please feel free to contact us by telephone at 855-270-6625, by email at [privacy@kohls.com](mailto:privacy@kohls.com) or click [here](https://www.kohls.com/privacy).

You may also write to us at the following address:

Kohl's Department Stores, Inc.  
P.O. Box 3043  
Milwaukee, Wisconsin 53201 

If you have any questions, comments or concerns with respect to our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@kohls.com](mailto:privacy@kohls.com). This inbox may also be used for Nevada residents to submit a verified request to direct us to stop the sale of your covered information.

Back to Top

## CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION

You have certain choices about how we use your information.

**Email:**

  * Use the unsubscribe link on any Kohl's promotional emails.
  * Use this link to unsubscribe from all future promotional emails: <https://www.kohls.com/homepage/sale_alert_unsub.jsp>.

**Text Messages & Mobile Coupons:**

  * Follow the opt-out instructions provided in our text message or mobile coupon.

**Mobile Application and Location Based Services:**

  * If you have previously opted into Kohl's collection and use of location-based information through our mobile application, you may opt-out by adjusting the Settings on your mobile device.
  * You may opt-out of all location-based information collection by uninstalling the Kohl's mobile application and refraining from using Kohl's Wi-Fi Services available in Stores.

**Postal Mail:**

  * To be removed from our global marketing mailing lists send your request, including your full name and mailing address, to  
Kohl’s Department Stores, Inc.  
PO Box 3120  
Milwaukee, WI 53201 
  * Call Customer Service at (866) 887-8884

**Cookies & Similar Technologies:**

  * To learn how we - and our vendors - use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our **Do Not Track** policy, please click here to view our About Our Ads policy.

Back to Top

## CHANGES IN POLICY

From time to time, we may change our Policy. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our Platforms. Please check our Platforms periodically for updates. 

Back to Top

©2019 Kohl's Department Stores, Inc. All rights reserved.
